Finding Aid for the Herbert M. Webster Photographs, 1926-1955 MS.3338
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- #190: Tom Brightwell and Grogan below Crest of Grandfather, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 215)
- #191: English Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 216)
- #192: The Cabin. Last day of Vacation Camp, 1934 August 19; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 217)
- #193: Hike from Clingman's Dome to Silers. Very memorable trip, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 218)
- #194: English Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 219)
- #195: Mt. Kephart & the Jump-off, 1935 October 13; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 220)
- #195: Mt. Kephart & the Jump-off, 1935 October 13; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 221)
- #196: Mt. Kephart from Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 222)
- #197: Mt. Leconte from Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 223)
- #198: State Line near Saw Trail. Dry Sluice Gap in foreground. Far points are Kephart-jump-off. Center right is Charlies Bunion, 1935 October 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 224)
- #199: Mt. Guyot & Mt. Chapman. From trail near Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 225)
- #199: Mt. Guyot & Mt. Chapman. From trail near Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 226)
- #200: [Mt.] Guyot from trail near Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 227)
- #201: Greenbrier Pinnacle (series) from State Line near Laurel Top, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 228)
- #202: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 229)
- #203: The Saw Teeth. Hike came up from left just beyond second Knob in foreground. Rough!, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 230)
- #204: Charley's Bunion, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 231)
- #204: Charley's Bunion, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 232)
- #205: Mitchie - 1st trip to Greenbrier. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 233)
- #206: North Carolina Side of Spence field. Note the old trail worn deep by many passing feet, 1935 April 14; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 234)
- #207: Stream in the Chilhowee, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 235)
- #207: Stream in the Chilhowee, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 236)
- #208: Mildred (Sister) & Katheryn Greenlee - down Walter Prong from the Jump-off, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 237)
- #209: L-R. Clyde Kitts, Maurice Webster, Virgie Boruff & Herb under Rainbow Falls (John Donaldson apparently made picture), undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 238)
- #209: L-R. Clyde Kitts, Maurice Webster, Virgie Boruff & Herb under Rainbow Falls (John Donaldson apparently made picture), undated; (1 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 239)
- #210: Spence Field, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 240)
- #211: Myrtle Point. Self Seated, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 241)
- #212-213A: Greenbrier Pinnacle. Guyot lead from Myrtle Point, 1934 March 25; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 242)
- #213B: State Line & Pinnacle from Myrtle Point. Trip up Bear Pen Holler, 1934 March 22; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 243)
- #214: Group. Place unidentified, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 244)
- #214: Group. Place unidentified, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 245)
- #215: Guyot & Old Black from White Rock, 1934 September 3; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 246)
- #216: Leconte from Pitman Center, 1934 June 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 247)
- #217: Mt. Mitchell faintly outlined in the distance from Grandfather Mountain, 1934 May 6; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 248)
- #218: English Mtn., undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 249)
- #218: English Mtn., undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 250)
- #219: Whaley boy who smoked logs from wrecked Cabin to go in the Cabin in the Brier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 251)
- #220: Could be road over Rich Mtn.?, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 252)
- #220: Could be road over Rich Mtn.?, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 253)
- #221: The Cabin in the Brier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 254)
- #222: Siler's Bald from tower on Blanket Mtn. (background), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 255)
- #223: Harvey Broome [at] Jump-off, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 256)
- #224: Mt. Leconte from Tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 257)
- #225: Dutch [Roth] [at] Porters Creek, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 258)
- #226: Guyot & Chapman from Laurel Top. The Ridge in the foreground is the State Line between Laurel Top & Pecks Corner, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 259)
- #227: Sweep of State Line with Mt. Chapman to extreme left & Eagle Rocks to extreme right, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 260)
- #228: Rich Mtn. from tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 261)
- #228: Rich Mtn. from tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 262)
- #229: Cold Springs Knob from Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 263)
- #229A: Mt. Chapman in Center - Guyot to the left. [F]rom trail near Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 264)
- #229A: Mt. Chapman in Center - Guyot to the left. [F]rom trail near Laurel Top, 1935 October 13; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 265)
- #230: Leconte from Silers Bald, 1935 December 15; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 266)
- #231: Thunderhead from tower on Blanket Mtn., 1934 October 14; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 267)
- #232: CCC Camp near Mt. Sterling Po., 1934 August 2; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 268)
- #233: [?] Turrentine at Double Springs Gap. Trip to Siler's from Clingmans, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 269)
- #234: Hoarfrost. Double Springs Gap. Clingmans to Silers, 1935 December 15; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 270)
- #234: Hoarfrost. Double Springs Gap. Clingmans to Silers, 1935 December 5; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 271)
- #235: Snow in the Sugarlands, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 272)
- #236: Special. Historic hike up Roaring Fork to Leconte. Picture made just after we topped out at the spring below the Lodge, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 273)
- #237: Sister Mildred on Cliff Top. Mt. Leconte, 1936 January 12; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 274)
- #238: Grotto Falls. Roaring Fork, 1936 January 12; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 275)
- #239: Brushy from Spur on side of Leconte, 1936 January 12; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 276)
- #240: Old Indian Head at Cliff Top, 1936 January 12; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 277)
- #240: Old Indian Head at Cliff Top, 1936 January 12; (2 of 3); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 278)
- #240: Old Indian Head at Cliff Top, 1936 January 12; (3 of 3); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 279)
- #241: Trail to Halls Top. Eleanor & Charlie, 1936 February 9; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 280)
- #242: Snow trail to Halls Top. Harvey Broome in background, 1936 February 9; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 281)
- #243: The English Mtn. from Trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 282)
- #244: Snow Trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 283)
- #245: Looking across to English Mtn. from trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (1 of 4); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 284)
- #245: Looking across to English Mtn. from trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (2 of 4); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 285)
- #245: Looking across to English Mtn. from trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (3 of 4); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 286)
- #245: Looking across to English Mtn. from trail to Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (4 of 4); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 287)
- #246: Snow covered valley, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 288)
- #247: Laurel Falls. Snow & Ice, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 289)
- #248: Trickling Falls on Road Prong, 1936 March 22; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 290)
- #248: Trickling Falls on Road Prong, 1936 March 22; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 291)
- #249: Mildred & Eleanor in Deep snow on difficult hike up Road Prong to Indian Gap. Left early a.m. did not get back to car until after 7.00 PM, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 292)
- #250: Road Prong in the snow, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 293)
- #251: Mountain Home near Cosby (Regantown), 1936 February; (1 of 2); (Damaged Negative) (Box 1, Folder 294)
- #251: Mountain Home near Cosby (Regantown), 1936 February; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 295)
- #252: Silers Bald from the Leapoff on Miry Ridge, 1936 February 16; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 296)
- #253: End view of Cabin in the Brier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 297)
- #254: Mildred & Eleanor. [D]eep snow - Road Prong, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 298)
- #255: Deep Snow. Road Prong. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 299)
- #256: Rare picture of little Cabin standing in early years near trail to Porters Creek below the barn. Notice open field - now overgrown. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 300)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (1 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 301)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (2 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 302)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (3 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 303)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (4 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 304)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (5 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 305)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (6 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 306)
- #257: Group at Big Chestnut. Porters Flats, undated; (7 of 7); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 307)
- #258: Trillium, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 308)
- #259: Trillium in Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 309)
- #260: Little Tub mill just above Tapoco on trail to Hangover. This primitive mill washed away in a later flood. Special, 1936 May 24; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 310)
- #261: Clingman's Dome from Partons Lookout on Miry Ridge, 1936 February 16; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 311)
- #262: Madrons Bald with the long lead to the right. Old Black is the dark mass to the left center. (Guyot is just behind), 1936 June 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 312)
- #263: The perfect silence. Hiker on a log. Guyot Spring. Subject of one incident on Once upon a mountain, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 313)
- #264: Mt. Sterling from trail between Guyot & Tri Corner Knob, 1936 June 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 314)
- #265: Lufty Knob from Hell Ridge, 1936 June 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 315)
- #266: Cliff Top from trail (snow), 1936 June 7; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 316)
- #266: Cliff top from trail (snow), 1936 June 7; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 317)
- #267: Low Gap. Start of trip to White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 318)
- #268: Looking toward White Rock from trail below Guyot, 1936 June 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 319)
- #269: White Rock in Center background. From trail below Guyot, 1936 June 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 320)
- #270(1): Gregory from Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 321)
- #270(2): Cades Cove from Rich Mtn., 1936 August 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 322)
- #272: Cades Cove & Thunderhead from Rich Mtn., 1936 August 23; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 323)
- #273: Eagle rock (In center background). Picture made from the Bradley Lookout on the State Line, 1936 November 29; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 324)
- #273: Eagle rock (In center background). Picture made from the Bradley Lookout on the State Line, 1936 November 29; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 325)
- #274: Mt. Leconte from trail beyond Dry Sluice Gap going East, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 326)
- #274: Mt. Leconte from trail beyond Dry Sluice Gap going East, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 327)
- #275: Mt. Leconte from trail beyond Dry Sluice Gap going East, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 328)
- #276: Mt. Leconte from State Line near Dry Sluice Gap, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 329)
- #277: Charlie & Eleanor walking thru a gap. Similar to one of Dutch [Roth] at Low Gap-White Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 330)
- #278: Leconte from Mt. Kephart, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 331)
- #279: Bald foreground. Mtn. range in distance. Halls Cabin?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 332)
- #280: Greenbrier Pinnacle from State Line trail near Laurel Top, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 333)
- #281: John Oliver Cabin. Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 334)
- #282: Eagle Rock Creek. Made on return from Labor Day hike, 1936 September 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 335)
- #283: Ramsey Cascades, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 336)
- #284: Unidentified image, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 337)
- #285: Self on Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 338)
- #286: Porters Creek, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 339)
- #287: Leconte from brink of Ramsey Cascades (Nice framing with rhodendron foliage to right), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 340)
- #288: Leconte from brink of Ramsey Cascades, 1936 September 6; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 341)
- #289: Snow trip to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 342)
- #290: Snow trip to Leconte. Alum Cove, 1936 December 20; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 343)
- #290: Snow trip to Leconte. Alum Cove, 1936 December 20; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 344)
- #291: Cliff Top - Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 345)
- #292: Snow trip to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 346)
- #292: Snow trip to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 347)
- #293: Fairy Land. Snow Trip to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 348)
- #294: Leconte Lodge, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 349)
- #295: Leconte Trip. Alum Cave Bluffs. [?] offered some peril as they loosened and fell with a great crash, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 350)
- #296: Alum Cave trail to Leconte (frozen overhead projection), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 351)
- #297: Leconte trip in snow. Near Arch Rock, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 352)
- #298: Anakeesta Ridge from Alum Cave trail, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 353)
- #299: Little bridge in snow near Arch Rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 354)
- #300: Leconte in Snow, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 355)
- #301: Sugarlands. From Alum Cave trail, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 356)
- #302: Looking west from Alum Cave trail to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 357)
- #303: Snow drifted to great depth here (site of a great slide) [on Leconte], 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 358)
- #304: Charley & Eleanor. Snow hike to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 359)
- #305: Anakeesta Ridge from Alum Cave Trail, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 360)
- #306: Self - Trip to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 361)
- #307: Leconte in snow, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 362)
- #308: Leconte in snow, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 363)
- #309: Leconte in snow, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 364)
- #310: Leconte in snow. [Chas.] DuBois, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 365)
- #311: Leconte in snow. Chas. DuBois, 1936 December 20; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 366)
- #311: Leconte in snow. Chas. DuBois, 1936 December 20; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 367)
- #312: A little waterfall on the wild and untrailed Roaring Fork, 1937 February 13; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 368)
- #313: Looking over the Hangover Lead to Lake Santeetlah (from Strattons Bald), 1937 April 15; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 369)
- #314: Beckman on Hangover, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 370)
- #315: Bald River Falls, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 371)
- #316: Strattons Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 372)
- #317: Odd tree, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 373)
- #318: Little Fodderstack from Stratton's Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 374)
- #319: Gregory from Hangover, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 375)
- #320: From Hangover - to Stanteetlah Valley (Herrick Brown), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 376)
- #321: Yellow creek mts. in the middle background, showing Yellow Creek Valley. Dark masses in foreground all leads to Hangover, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 377)
- #322: Could be Bald River. Rough water, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 378)
- #323: Strattons Bald - Dimly seen to left background in Big Frog Mtn. near Etowah, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 379)
- #324: Big Huckleberry from Strattons Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 380)
- #325: Little Huckleberry from Strattons Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 381)
- #326: Beech Gap, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 382)
- #327: Hoai. Between Strattons Bald & Strawberry Knob, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 383)
- #328: Tree pressed against rock, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 384)
- #329: Rough waterfall. Bald River?, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 385)
- #330: Yellow Creek Valley from Hangover. State Line near Thunderhead in background, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 386)
- #331: Looking down from Hangover to State Line - Smoky range. Lower dams below Santeetlah Creek. Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 387)
- #332: Roaring Fork, 1937 March 7; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 388)
- #333: Gibson Inn, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 389)
- #334: Looking out at Gibson Inn, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 390)
- #335: Gibson Inn, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 391)
- #336: Noland's Creek (The coldest day!) Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 392)
- #337: Christmas tree. Andrews Bald, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 393)
- #338: Looking west from Andrews Bald. The Coldest Day, 1937 November 21; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 394)
- #339: Charlie bends his back to bitter wind down Nolands creek. The Coldest Day, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 395)
- #340: Roma Robertson (Bowmaster) at Rockytop Thunderhead, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 396)
- #341: Cades Cove from Rocky Top (Thunderhead) with Duck Mtn. in right background, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 397)
- #342: Sunset. Rocky Top. Thunderhead, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 398)
- #343: Unidentified image, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 399)
- #344: The Great Cascades. Roaring Fork, 1937 March 1; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 400)
- #345: Some one goes up for a look, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 401)
- #346: Tom Brightwell on trail from Gant back to Gregory Creek, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 402)
- #347: Special negative of John Oliver Home. Cades Cove, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 403)
- #348: Alum Cave trail to Leconte, 1936 December 20; (Damaged Negative) (Box 1, Folder 404)
- #349: Anakeesta Ridge. Cliff Top looks very cold & very far away at this point, 1936 December 20; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 405)
- #350: Stream. Potters flats or Chilhowee, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 406)
- #351: East end of Spence Field? Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 407)
- #352: Clingmans Dome trail from Tremont, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 408)
- #353: Harvey Broome. Tremont to Clingmans Dome, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 409)
- #354: Bear!, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 410)
- #355: Clingmans Dome from Tremont, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 411)
- #357: The Cabin in Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 412)
- #358: Harvey Broome - Roaring Fork, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 413)
- #360: East End of Spence Field, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 414)
- #361: Roaring Fork, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 415)
- #362: Early work trip. Prof. Duncan Supt. Jean Wooster left foreground. Guy Frizzell & Tom Duncan on roof, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 416)
- #363: Elvie Manley. Prof. Duncan, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 417)
- This was a lovely stream just across the road from Willie Myers place, Cades Cove, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 418)
- This was a lovely stream just across the road from Willie Myers place, Cades Cove, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 419)
- #364: Mildred Webster (Miller). With Whaley boy & his horse (dragging logs from dismantled cabins), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 420)
- #365: Foreground: Tom Duncan, Elvie Manley, Mrs. Jim Webster; Roof: Tom Duncan, Guy Frizzell, Sonny Morris, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 421)
- #366: Cabin work trip, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 422)
- #367: Very early picture of barn on Cabin site. Greenbrier before restoration. Now surrounded by 2nd growth timber, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 423)
- #368: Old Messer Place. First work trip to Cabin site. Note condition of spring house, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 424)
- #369: Cabin in the 'Brier, 1934 August 19; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 425)
- #369: Cabin in the 'Brier, 1934 August 19; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 1, Folder 426)
- #370: Early Cabin Work Trip. Time out for lunch, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 427)
- #371: Herb & Tom Connell on the roof, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 428)
- #372: Well built Cabin in the Greenbrier. It was from Cabins such as this that we took logs for out building of the Hiking Club Cabin, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 429)
- #373: Wrecking old cabin for good timbers to be used in the Hiking Club Cabin (Note young Whaley & his horse on left), undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 430)
- #374: Cabin at the Fittified Spring, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 431)
- #375: Old barn in the Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 432)
- #376: Cabin just above the Messer place - Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 433)
- #377: Cabin in the Brier. Note open areas - now grown up, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 434)
- #378: Small, but well made Cabin near Messer site, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 435)
- #379: Unidentified image, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 436)
- #380: Early work day at the Messer site, undated; (Negative) (Box 1, Folder 437)
- #381: Hiking Club group at Fittified Spring. Charlie Gibson at extreme right; Harriett Foulkes center; Jim Webster facing spring, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- #382: Harvey has a tall story. Cherry Orchard. Ramsey Prong, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- #383: Campfire just outside Cabin in Greenbrier. Top Row: Chas. Gibson - West Barber - Roger Howell - Herb Webster - Jim Webster; 2nd Row: Jesse Dempster - Dickerman - Mrs. Jim Webster - Harriett Foulkes. Others not identified, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- #384: Cabin in the Greenbrier (In contrast to other cabins, this one is weatherboarded), undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- #385: Hikers on trail far below the summit of Grandfather Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- #386: A very fine barn in the Greenbrier Cove near the cabin. Well constructed, it was just as carefully [?] as its owners cabin (Note the large cleared area; Now covered with heavy second growth forest), undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- #387: Scouting trip to Thunderhead via Bote Mtn. [with] Tom Duncan, Tom Brightwell, Tom Conner, [and] Herb Webster. Tom D. is trying to discourage hound dog from following us, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- #388: Drinkwater Pool, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- #389: Swinging bridge near Sevierville, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- #390: The Chimney Saddle. Picture made by Jim Francis, circa 1928; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- #390: The Chimney Saddle. Picture made by Jim Francis, circa 1928; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- #391: Hikers on Myrtle Point, Leconte, 1934 March 25; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 12)